{
    "subject": "resource/Neethaane_En_Ponvasantham",
    "predicate": "ontology/cinematography",
    "object": "resource/M._S._Prabhu",
    "human_readable": "The cinematography of Neethaane En Ponvasantham was done by M. S. Prabhu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.961310625076294,
            "question": "Who was responsible for the cinematography of Neethaane En Ponvasantham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8672974705696106,
            "question": "Which film features the work of M. S. Prabhu as cinematographer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7092486619949341,
            "question": "Can you name other notable films with M. S. Prabhu's cinematography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48946136236190796,
            "question": "What is M. S. Prabhu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4725099503993988,
            "question": "What is the role of a cinematographer in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3416754901409149,
            "question": "What are some common techniques used in cinematography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2916604280471802,
            "question": "What makes a film's cinematography memorable?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2314097285270691,
            "question": "What are some awards or recognitions given for exceptional cinematography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20478753745555878,
            "question": "How does cinematography influence the mood and tone of a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14176629483699799,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Gautham Menon."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The cinematography of Neethaane En Ponvasantham was done by M. S. Prabhu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3915_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does cinematography influence the mood and tone of a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3915_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some awards or recognitions given for exceptional cinematography?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3915_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes a film's cinematography memorable?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3915_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3915_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state, \"CINEMATOGRAPHY by MS Prabhu and Om Prakash is, for the most part, brilliant\" in relation to Neethaane En Ponvasantham. Additionally, \"Production > Cinematography M. S Prabhu\" from another document confirms that M. S. Prabhu was indeed the cinematographer for the film, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}